Speaker 1: So,
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): you're Enrique Terrio of Proud Boys fame, is that right? That is correct. Now, refresh my memory. Were you pardoned or what went on legally with you most recently? I was pardoned. I'm the only one
out of
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): 12 individuals that were
Speaker 3: wrongfully charged with sedition
Speaker 4: that was pardoned.
Now,
Speaker 4: if memory serves, you were not even in physically Washington, D.C. on January 6th. Is that right?
Speaker 5: I'm the only January 6th defendant that was not in the District of Columbia.
Speaker 6: I'm actually the only January 6th defendant that wasn't on Capitol grounds. Weren't you in Baltimore or something? I was in Baltimore about like 80
miles
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): away. And remind me what the theory was for charging you despite your not even being physically present.
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): The theory was that I'm the leader of the Proud Boys, and I
Speaker 7: instructed my guys to go in, and as cool... Stand back and stand by, right? And as cool as
Speaker 8: that sounds, that I was puppeteering the American insurrection... You and the Oath Keepers and all those guys. It's not true. And as a
Speaker 9: pardon man, if I really did it, I could say it right now and face no consequences.
Speaker 9: But
Speaker 10 (higher-pitched voice): I didn't. Did you frame the official pardon notice or
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): anything like that? Did you get a copy of the letter or declaration? Yeah, so I got what's called a
Speaker 3: certificate of pardon from the Department of Justice. It's not a signed document by the president, because that's not how these pardons worked. He kind of just, it was kind of like a blanket pardon. So it was the day he came
Speaker 11: back into office,
Speaker 3: right? He
Speaker 11: pardoned all the January
Speaker 3: 6th related defendants. Correct. It was...
It was his
Speaker 3: first act as the 47th president of the United States to pardon us.
Speaker 12: Really? Yes.
Speaker 4: Okay.
How did that
Speaker 4: feel when the news of that came down? You know... Because I should clarify, I have some issues right now with Trump politically in terms of some of the governing choices, but I was always...
Speaker 4: pretty adamant that there was a ton of overcharging going on with respect to January 6th. They would bring in
Speaker 10 (higher-pitched voice): these post-sentencing terrorism enhancements and all this other nonsense that quote-unquote progressives would ordinarily probably be a little bit skeptical of just on the merits, but because this was a huge domestic terrorism incident or something like that, insurrection, blah, blah, blah, blah, they look the other way. I had the same position.
Speaker 13: if you went into the capitol you should get hit with trespassing although there's i think there's an argument that they've
Speaker 14: been making if you assaulted a police officer you should be charged with that but the problem wasn't that they were charging the trespassers uh with 20-year felonies if you assaulted a police officer you were getting triple the time of the same charge at some other
Speaker 16: some other event or at some other
Speaker 15: incident so that's where i think the problem came in the justice system,
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): it wasn't even.
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): So, what brings you to this rally? You're Cuban by ethnicity, right? I'm Cuban-American. I was born here.
Speaker 17: And,
Speaker 18 (higher-pitched voice): you know, I think I'm very supportive of the president and his actions in Venezuela. I'm also, I believe, not something similar, but I think that we're going to see that with
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): Cuba in the next three weeks. So, I'm out here showing support. I'm also out here covering the event. So, we're going
Speaker 20: to see some sort of military action in Cuba?
I would
Speaker 20: be okay with it.
Is that
Speaker 20: what you've heard might
Speaker 21: be happening in the next three weeks? No, no. What I could speculate is that they're going to take some
Speaker 24 (higher-pitched voice): extra diplomatic solution first. And if that
Speaker 25: doesn't work, Canel and the Castros will end up like Maduro. Because
a lot of
Speaker 24 (higher-pitched voice): people here that I've been speaking to, they outright are advocating for some kind of military action. It's
a
Speaker 24 (higher-pitched voice): I support it. I support it. Look, there's nothing more America first
Speaker 26 (higher-pitched voice): than American supremacy in the Western Hemisphere. What about doing regime change? I mean, I thought
Speaker 8: some people who were MAGA were a little bit more skeptical of that idea. Some people, some of my colleagues on the right don't like it.
Speaker 28 (higher-pitched voice): I'm not a dub.
Speaker 28 (higher-pitched voice): - I don't want wars in the Middle East. I support limited strikes in Iran.
Speaker 29: - Wait, so what do you think of the Iran situation? Those aren't limited strikes. This is a pretty extensive campaign right
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): now. - It's starting to get extensive. - They're sending ground troops. - Do I like it? No, but I think the president
has a
Speaker 30: lot more information
Speaker 28 (higher-pitched voice): than we do. And I trusted him with my life, with my pardon. I think I could trust him with this. - So you would trust him to say, look, we gotta occupy this island in
Speaker 26 (higher-pitched voice): the Persian Gulf with Marines. Like, that would be
Speaker 31: okay. Like, how far could it go where you'd be willing to tolerate it? - I don't want boots on the ground. - That's on its way.
Speaker 31: Another thing is, it's not
Speaker 30: my beat. You know, my beat is more domestic issues, and issues that are happening on this side of the hemisphere. Is it a make or break for me? Absolutely not. What
Speaker 26 (higher-pitched voice): do you think of the whole Jeffrey Epstein issue? You know, a lot of people on the right were upset with how Trump was handling that, or Pam Bondi, or whomever.
Speaker 26 (higher-pitched voice): What was your opinion, if you have
Speaker 32: one, on that before Trump came in this past term, and what is your view now, to the extent that you followed it or had a view? Okay, so I'll start again with the Epstein stuff isn't my beat, but I do think Pam Bondi holds a brunt of what she said because we got confusing statements from her. They're on
Speaker 28 (higher-pitched voice): my desk. They're not on my desk. They don't exist. They exist. Oh, we're allowing them. I think Pan Bondi's
game.
Speaker 28 (higher-pitched voice): got to go well trump said the whole thing was a hoax i think that i think that uh a lot of people misread what he said there when he said democratic hoax the democrats
Speaker 34: are spinning it in a way
Speaker 35: such that they're
Speaker 34: trying to attack
Speaker 30: trump yes and i think that's where i don't think he worded what he was saying right also because he said it in other interviews i had nothing to do with the you know release them he said that before so well he tried to
Speaker 37: block the legislation to do that for a until the support
and contract
Speaker 37: was overwhelming, and then he had to
sign
Speaker 7: it. - Yeah, but again, that's not a make or break issue for me. - Sure,
Speaker 10 (higher-pitched voice): but whether or not it's a make or break issue, like what is your ultimate sort of synthesis of that issue? Like what do you, do you think Jeff Ripson was running a pedophile
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): trafficking ring that ensnared all these prominent people? - I believe so, I believe so. Just based on like
Speaker 5: emails that I've seen that come from the DOJ website, it looks like there was something
going on.
What do
Speaker 38: you make of the references to pizza and that sort of thing that people were making a big deal about? Do you think
Speaker 39: that's over-interpreting, or is that really some kind of coded reference to some kind of child
Speaker 40: sex rhyme? Take your time. I'm sorry, I get yawning spells.
Speaker 41: That
Speaker 11: happens a lot when people are around me. They get so overwhelmed that they have all these reflexive physical reactions. I
Speaker 7: think it does. I think it had a coded meaning.
Speaker 7: If you read it, normal people don't talk like that.
Speaker 43: I just
-- but
Speaker 43: I'm not an expert. -But you don't hold Trump responsible for any of it? Like, doesn't the buck stop with him if his administration is screwing
it up?
Speaker 43: -No, I think the buck stops at Pam Bondi there. -But
Speaker 44: who appointed Pam Bondi? -I think it was a bad appointment. I can tell you that. But she's tasked with doing a job. Do I think she's going
to get --
she's
Speaker 44: going to get resigned
Speaker 45: or fired, I think so. I think we'll see that after midterms.
Speaker 46: Okay. All right. Enrique Terrio, have
a great
Speaker 46: evening. Thank
you. Yeah.